[{"answer": " Y", "docId": "Juno.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "Is this Juno", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "I know. Women Now, I guess. The commercial says they help women now", "docId": "Juno.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "Eh, I'll call them myself. But I do need your help with something very urgent", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "So, what do you think we should do", "docId": "Juno.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "Yeah, typically. That's what happens when our moms and teachers get pregnant", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "Yeah, wizard, I guess. I mean do what you think is right", "docId": "Juno.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "Whose idea was it", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "You know, you've been acting like this ever since I went up to see my brother at that place. I told you, nothing happened", "docId": "Juno.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "What? My eyes are not lying", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "Something happened. Because your eyes? Are very cold? They're very cold, my friend. They're cold, lying eyes", "docId": "Juno.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "Yes they are, my friend. Since Mankato, they have been lying eyes", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "I know. Maybe they'll canonize me for being so selfless", "docId": "Juno.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "my friend and I were going to go to that place for spring break", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": " Oh", "docId": "Juno.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "Sorry. I swear I'm not a gear snob", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "A Pilates machine", "docId": "Juno.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "You don't make anything. It's for exercising", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": " The Wizard of my friend", "docId": "Juno.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "Please. my friend is the ultimate master of horror", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "Nothing..", "docId": "Juno.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "I went to the doctor today", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "Um, I think people are kind of unsure about the situation because it's not, you know, set in stone", "docId": "Juno.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "No, no, I don't think that, my friend. It's just that, we went through a situation before where it didn't work out", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "Listen, Bre", "docId": "Juno.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "You don't know anything about me", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "It doesn't work that way, kiddo. You don't know squat about the dynamics of marriage", "docId": "Juno.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "I know enough", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "What about my friend? You could go out with my friend", "docId": "Juno.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "I totally heard you did", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "Well, I wanted to pick something gende", "docId": "Juno.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "I think I'm leaning toward Custard in this light. I don't know. I should paint a small area..", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": "Wow, someone's been actually doing her geometry homework for once", "docId": "Juno.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": "Please do not refer to Mr. my friend as", "qsentId": 34}, {"answer": "Um, hi", "docId": "Juno.txt", "asentId": 37, "question": "Yeah, I did ask her if she wanted to go. A bunch of us from the team are going to that place, then the prom, then my friend's parents' cabin", "qsentId": 36}, {"answer": "Forget it, my friend. Take Katrina the Douche Packer to the prom. I'm sure you guys will have a really bitchin' time", "docId": "Juno.txt", "asentId": 39, "question": "I still have your virginity", "qsentId": 38}, {"answer": " But you're old", "docId": "Juno.txt", "asentId": 41, "question": "I don't know. I just liked being your friend. I sort of liked becoming furniture in your weird life", "qsentId": 40}, {"answer": "Yeah, downtown", "docId": "Juno.txt", "asentId": 43, "question": "It's a loft", "qsentId": 42}, {"answer": "You're a part time lover and a fulltime friend. The monkey on your back is the latest trend. I don't see what anyone can see, in anyone else but you", "docId": "Juno.txt", "asentId": 45, "question": "We both have shiny happy fits of rage. You want more fans, I want more stage. I don't see what anyone can see, in anyone else but you", "qsentId": 44}, {"answer": "Here is the church and here is the steeple. We sure are cute for two ugly people. I don't see what anyone can see, in anyone else but you", "docId": "Juno.txt", "asentId": 47, "question": "You are always trying to keep it real. I'm in love with how you feel. I don't see what anyone can see, in anyone else but you", "qsentId": 46}, {"answer": "We both have shiny happy fits of rage. You want more fans, I want more stage. I don't see what anyone can see, in anyone else but you", "docId": "Juno.txt", "asentId": 49, "question": "I kiss you on the brain in the shadow of a train. I kiss you all starryeyed, my body's swinging from side to side. I don't see what anyone can see, in anyone else but you", "qsentId": 48}, {"answer": "You are always trying to keep it real. I'm in love with how you feel. I don't see what anyone can see, in anyone else but you", "docId": "Juno.txt", "asentId": 51, "question": "The pebbles forgive me, the trees forgive me. So why can't you forgive me? I don't see what anyone can see, in anyone else but you", "qsentId": 50}]